freeadvertz.com 2013-06-19

# Privacy Statement

## [workathomebusinesssuccess.com](http://www.workathomebusinesssuccess.com/) Privacy Statement

In order to demonstrate our commitment to our visitors’ privacy, we disclose our information practices. We will keep to these practice guidelines on ALL occasions in our dealings with you. 

You won’t find a long winded, attorney-driven, hard-to-understand Privacy Statement here. Simply put: 

We will **NEVER** distribute, share or sell any personal information we collect on our website to any third party.  
We will **NEVER** spam your email address.

If you are interested, here are the details on information collection and use at  
**[workathomebusinesssuccess.com](http://www.workathomebusinesssuccess.com/)**. 

**Information Collection**

**[workathomebusinesssuccess.com](http://www.workathomebusinesssuccess.com/)** is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We collect information from our visitors at several different points. 

**Newsletter**  
If a visitor wishes to subscribe our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We then send newsletters to visitor’s email address. 

**Autoresponder**  
When a visitor requests information such as our free e-book, courses, etc, by sending email to our autoresponder, the visitor’s email address is logged. The requested information will be sent out automatically. 

This includes not only filling up a form at our website. The same progress happens whenever a visitor sends email to our autoresponder, through a form at our site, using his/her own email client, from another website, from newsgroup… 

**Order**  
We, or our credit card processing partner, request information from customer on our order form. A customer must provide contact information (such as name, email address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the customer. 

**Feedback form**  
Visitors may communicate with us by filling out feedback form at our website. The feedback content itself together with related email address will be stored for our future reference. 

**Communication**  
Visitors may communicate with us by sending emails to our email address stated on our website. This includes, but not limited to, feedback, sales information, technique support, order enquire, etc. 

The communication content itself together with related email address will be stored for our future reference and for us to serve visitors better. 

**Tell a Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address.

**Information Use**

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor’s computer tied to information about the visitor. However, usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Cookies can be removed any time from visitor’s computer. Refer browser help file for instructions. 

By setting a cookie on our site, first time visitors would see a popup window inviting him/her to subscribe our newsletter. Cookies enable us to track whether he/she is a returning visitor. If a visitor comes back to our site within a short period of time (2 days, for example), the popup window will not appear again. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this web site are delivered to visitors by our web advertising partner. Information about visit to this site, such as number of times visitors have viewed an ad (but not email address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about our web advertising partner, cookies, and how to “opt-out”, please visit our web advertising partner’s site. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by  
**[workathomebusinesssuccess.com](http://www.workathomebusinesssuccess.com/)** only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitor’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. These information are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Newsletter**  
We send confirmation and welcome message to subscribers once they subscribe our free newsletter. Regular newsletters will then be sent to subscribers. The frequency we send newsletter is stated at the relative newsletter subscription page. 

Out of respect for our subscribers privacy, we provide a way to opt-out (unsubscribe) of our newsletter. Please see also the Choice and Opt-out sections. 

We will never distribute, share or sell subscribers’ personal information to any third party unless it’s requested by law. 

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement to our newsletter subscribers and customers. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send them an email. These communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with visitors and customers to provide requested services and information, in accordance with the their wishes. We will try to answer all correspondence in a timely fashion. 

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**  
We may need to reveal aggregated demographic information to our advertisers in the future. This is normally necessary to get quality sponsors and advertisers. These information are not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact us to request the removal of this information from our database.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve visitor privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website. 

**Third Party Intermediaries**  
We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. The company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Business Transitions**  
In the event  
**[workathomebusinesssuccess.com](http://www.workathomebusinesssuccess.com/)** goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, visitors’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Subscribers and customers will be notified via prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the visitors’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our subscribers and customers are given the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used by us. 

Visitors who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and other communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking the unsubscribe link in the newsletter or email us at: **[webmaster@workathomebusinesssuccess.com](mailto:webmaster@workathomebusinesssuccess.com)**

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we,  
**[workathomebusinesssuccess.com](http://www.workathomebusinesssuccess.com/)** , are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time to time our site may request information from visitors via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the visitors (and subscribers, customers) therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless requested by law. 

**Security**  
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our order form asks customers to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our visitors’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. 

**Children**

**[workathomebusinesssuccess.com](http://www.workathomebusinesssuccess.com/)** does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe we have received any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our visitors are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use visitors’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect visitor information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

**Email:**  

**Address:**  
PO Box 1172  
Belfast  
BT13 2RX  
Ireland
